Ms. Liu, slow down, Ms. Liu.
Slow down, slow down.
Slow down, Ms. Liu.
What's wrong?
Boss Li.
Ms. Liu is here.
Where are you feeling unwell?
Where am I feeling unwell?
We're asking you.
My whole body...
Whole body...
My head hurts.
You have heads all over your body?
No, you mean a headache, right?
Here, let me take a look.
Do you have a fever?
Let's check the temperature.
That feels much better.
Ms. Liu, you have magic hands.
No, his temperature isn't high.
It's just...
Why is there so much cold sweat?
Exactly.
Perhaps...
I was infected by Professor Fan.
I've been taking care of the patient non-stop these days.
Maybe it triggered my...
old chronic insomnia...
and flared it up.
Illness really comes like a landslide.
Ms. Liu.
I'm sorry about this.
It's okay.
This time...
I'm afraid I'll have to trouble you again.
It's fine.
You really treat Ms. Liu like a professional caregiver.
She took care of me because...
Right?
As for you...
I think we should call...
Zhu Zhu and Yusheng to come take care of you.
Or just have Dr. Chang send a male caregiver.
Come back.
Why is it that when you were sick,
you had Ms. Liu to take care of you?
But when I'm sick,
I get a male caregiver?
It's the same illness.
I demand the same treatment.
Old Li.
It hasn't been confirmed it's the same illness yet.
How about...
I go get Royal Physician Sun to take a look.
No.
Such a minor illness...
shouldn't disturb Royal Physician Sun.
I think...
Ms. Liu will do.
Alright, then...
Open your mouth.
Ahh.
I can't make sense of this either.
We should get a professional. Let...
Let Royal Physician Sun come...
and prescribe you some medicine or something.
I said no need, so no need.
Just take Professor Fan's...
leftover medicine...
give me two pills to try, that'll be enough.
It'd be a pity to throw the leftovers away.
I think...
I should just drink more water.
Ms. Liu, could you...
get me some hot water?
You want hot water, right?
I'll go pour it for you.
No.
Sister Cai.
You just go about your business.
You've been working hard these days too.
Managing a myriad of affairs is very exhausting.
We can't have you wearing yourself out.
Then I'll pour it for you.
That's even less necessary.
You just recovered.
I might infect you again.
If we keep cross-infecting each other like this,
it'll be even worse.
Then...
I'll go pour it for you.
That's the way.
Ms. Liu.
Sorry to trouble you.
You're welcome.
Boss Li, you're something else.
I just got over my illness and now you're sick.
What's so strange about that?
If you can be sick, why can't I?
Ms. Liu already diagnosed me.
A forehead full of cold sweat.
Does Ms. Liu count?
For a diagnosis,
you need a professional, right?
That's right.
What do you mean?
You don't trust Ms. Liu?
Right.
I don't trust myself either.
Better get a professional.
Summon Royal Physician Sun.
Yes, sir.
Yusheng, Zhu Zhu, summon the Royal Physician!
Say no more. Come.
Drink... drink some water.
There's nothing wrong.
Check a bit more carefully.
Don't be careless.
There isn't anything.
No murmurs.
No rales.
No abdominal bowel sounds.
Lungs,
bronchi...
How can there be nothing wrong?
Listen to this.
Sorry, Doctor.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Alright.
Nothing major wrong.
No, wait.
You can't be so hasty.
You didn't even check my pulse.
No need.
What's the point of checking the pulse?
Just making trouble.
No...
Won't you leave some medical advice, Royal Physician?
Keep the diet light.
Drink plenty of hot water.
What kind of advice is that?
Who doesn't know to drink hot water?
This patient really does need to drink plenty of hot water.
Because the human body
needs to flush out a lot of harmful substances.
Right.
But do you really count as a patient?
Did you hear that?
I need to flush out harmful substances.
Lots of them.
Hurry up and pour the water.
Ms. Liu,
please have a seat.
Alright.
Okay, I'll sit.
Good.
Take it easy.
Slow down, it's hot.
Slow down.
Want some more?
Tastes good.
It'd be sweeter with some sugar.
Grandpa Li.
You don't look like you have a cold to me.
Looks more like you drank too much hot water.
Exactly.
It's such a hot day.
You're chugging all this hot water.
And wrapped in such a thick quilt.
How could you not sweat?
Don't talk nonsense.
What do you know?
Ms. Liu even said...
But Boss Li...
You really don't look like you have a cold.
Right. How about this...
Stand up and take two steps.
Right.
You take two steps.
Take two steps.
Take two steps. Walk around.
Can you?
Try it.
Well...
Take two steps.
Right, you take two steps.
Here, take it slow.
Take it slow.
I'll hold you. Come on.
Look.
Look, once you stand up...
You look perfectly fine.
No, I mean, you clearly...
...are much better.
If you ask me...
There's absolutely nothing wrong with him.
You said it.
I think Grandpa Li should rest and cool off.
He'll be skipping to the cafeteria in no time.
I stood up!
That's amazing!
Ms. Liu.
You've cured my illness!
You have a pair of magical hands!
No...
I...
I'm not that capable.
Really, you look fine now.
Well then, you rest.
I'll be going back now.
Wait...
I'm heading back to the dorm too.
Bye, Grandpa Li.
Ms. Liu, about my flowers...
I got them. Thank you.
Flowers?
What flowers?
Old Li.
Why are you standing there?
You scared me.
In the middle of the night, out of nowhere...
...you let out a yelp.
You're the one who scared me.
What's so scary about me?
How are you not scary?
It's pitch black here.
You're standing there like a big stone monument.
Who wouldn't be scared seeing that at night?
What stone monument?
A stone sculpture.
Look at me.
Don't I look like a...
...statue standing tall...
...against the wind?
Oh, give it a rest.
Old Li, in the middle of the night...
...why are you standing there?
You're reflecting on your behavior...
...from this afternoon, right?
Not bad.
I did reflect for a while.
But after reflecting...
...I got insomnia.
Insomnia?
You can try counting sheep.
They say it works well.
I did.
I counted I don't know how many sheep.
The more I counted, the hungrier I got.
I started craving hot pot mutton.
Lamb skewers would work too.
You want a midnight snack?
Then don't think about sheep.
Think about something else.
I did.
Playing ping pong...
...swimming and stuff.
I thought about those too.
Just now, while you were grinding your teeth, snoring...
...and smacking your lips...
...I went through the breaststroke...
...I learned in the army...
...freestyle...
...even the doggy paddle...
...I went through them all.
It was no use.
You're talking nonsense.
Complete nonsense.
I don't snore.
How do you know you don't snore?
You've never shared a bed with anyone.
How would you know you don't snore?
Anyway, I don't.
You snore quite a lot.
And it comes in waves.
You snore and snore...
...then you stop breathing.
I even have to check...
...to see if you're breathing.
Scared you might die.
That's sleep apnea syndrome.
What is it?
It's sleep apnea syndrome.
You have this condition.
It seems when people get old...
...having someone nearby is really important.
Thank you, Old Li.
What's there to thank?
Just my luck to share a room with you.
Just have to put up with it.
Hello, Ms. Liu.
Morning, Ms. Liu.
You're up so early.
What early?
We didn't sleep at all.
Why?
It's all because...
...Little Fan had insomnia last night.
I took care of him all night.
What? Aren't you twisting the truth?
Clearly you had insomnia.
I chatted with you all night, okay?
I took care of him all night.
Alright.
Is this worth arguing about?
You don't understand nursing; you might make it worse.
Nursing is a job for us women.
In a bit...
...I'll go over and check on you guys.
By the way...
...who was the one with insomnia?
I... I had insomnia.
You?
You fight me for food at meals
You fight me for water in the shower
You fight me for the remote when watching TV
Now it's even better
You're even competing with me to be sick
You get jealous of everything you see
What is wrong with you?
Who's competing with you?
Yesterday you copied me having a fever
Chugging hot water like crazy
Who was that?
Enough
Didn't we agree?
We wouldn't expose each other's faults anymore
The one drinking hot water yesterday...
That was just an isolated incident
Don't you... with a sick person like me...
...keep pestering me unreasonably, okay?
I didn't sleep a wink all last night
Can't you cut me some slack?
Fine
I'll let you have your way
But who's going to cut me some slack?
I also didn't sleep a wink all night
Professor Fan
I know
To keep me company...
You also didn't sleep a wink all night
This fully shows how learned you are...
And highly respected
Dedicating your heart and talent...
...to us, the older generation
You are the one I admire and respect most...
The most lovable person
What I like is...
Stop right there
It's the exact same words...
But when you say them...
Why does it sound so awkward?
What's awkward about it?
So...
I hope you keep up this style
And go to sleep like a good boy
So that Ms. Liu...
Can treat me with peace of mind
I knew you were up to no good when you praised me
I'm telling you, this time I'm just...
Not giving in
How can you be like this?
Why can't I?
The business of insomnia...
Do you have a monopoly on it?
So only you are allowed...
To play at having insomnia?
And I can't be unable to sleep?
People fight over titles and honors...
But fighting to get sick?
Why should this doctor...
Be hogged by you alone?
You...
No...
How can you...
Be so unreasonable?
With you making such a fuss...
My head hurts even more
Although I have a history of insomnia...
It's not like I can have insomnia on command
This once-in-a-lifetime chance for me...
And you're fighting me for it?
How about this...
Ms. Liu is one person
And there are two of us
Which patient she takes care of...
Depends on who is sicker
From now on, I declare...
I officially have insomnia
Who's afraid of whom?
From now on...
Officially insomnia
Wait, that's not right
I started having insomnia yesterday
Boss Li, Professor Fan
Which one of you actually has insomnia?
Me
I have insomnia
I can't sleep night after night.
I can't close my eyes all night long.
You...
Look.
Whenever I scroll through TikTok,
I just...
get incredibly excited.
I toss and turn in bed like a pancake.
Once I lie down, if I get up to use the bathroom,
I just want to grab a book
and sit on the toilet all night.
I can't sleep at night.
I have no energy during the day.
I've lost my sleep.
I treat the night like the day.
And the day like the night... and like the day too.
Ms. Liu,
look at my eyes.
I look exactly like a panda.
These two big dark circles.
Ms. Liu,
look at my eyes.
Whatever a goldfish looks like,
that's what I look like.
Staring blankly,
without blinking.
It seems you two old brothers
are quite ill.
Who's brothers with him?
We have our own separate illnesses.
But I...
I'm just one person.
I can't take care of both of you.
Oh my goodness.
Boss Li, Professor Fan.
When I woke up this morning,
I heard you two were sick.
Oh, I was so worried.
I rolled over and fell right back asleep.
Look how that delayed things.
Ms. Liu,
if you need any help, just give a cough.
You're just in time.
What's wrong?
Ms. Liu,
this minor ailment of mine
is causing you so much trouble.
I'm really embarrassed.
Boss Li,
don't say that.
You hold a high position,
dominating the business world,
commanding thousands of troops,
creating immense wealth.
For the great rejuvenation of the Chinese nation,
you've made such a huge contribution.
I've always admired you the most,
such an influential figure.
Really.
Ms. Liu, do you really
have such an opinion of me?
I actually never felt it before.
I was too careless.
Too confused.
Too slow-witted.
But it doesn't matter.
We can start from now.
Time's up.
We agreed,
switch every ten minutes.
Time is up.
Time to switch.
Why should I?
On what grounds?
It's barely been five minutes.
Why switch now?
If you want to switch,
you have to wait for me to finish the story. Listen.
Right at this critical moment,
one could hear from inside the coffin...
Someone is crying.
Look at that coffin lid again.
Alright.
Time's up. Switch.
Old Fan.
I think you should just hurry up and sleep.
Sister Cai is telling such a wonderful story.
Isn't it just to coax you to sleep?
Once you fall asleep,
Sister Cai will naturally stop telling it.
I can't sleep.
If I sleep,
she...
...they...
won't they all leave?
You just can't bear for me to leave, right?
I knew it.
My story is so good.
Suspense, horror, mystery.
This story of mine,
"Red Braised Pork in the Morgue" is just captivating.
Right?
Listen to one part, you want two.
The more scared you are, the more you want to listen.
You don't want to sleep now, do you?
I'll continue telling you.
This coffin...
Okay.
I beg you.
I beg you, Sister.
Sister.
Even if I...
fall asleep,
I'd have fainted from your scare.
I'd have nightmares even in a coma.
Tell it to Old Li.
That works too.
To know what happens next,
please listen to the afternoon chapter.
Ms. Liu.
Switch.
Okay.
Professor Fan.
Do you feel any better?
As soon as you came over,
I felt much better.
Boss Li.
You've heard those old stories eight hundred times.
You don't care to listen anymore, right?
Let's try something original.
I'll tell you one I just finished reading.
Magical,
horror,
mystery novel.
"The Green Right Hand".
Green...
and a right hand?
If you want a left hand, I have that too.
No need.
Boss Li, don't be polite with me.
Ms. Liu told me,
you really love listening to stories.
And not only do you listen,
you also love telling them.
This is how you tell it:
Once upon a time there was a mountain.
In the mountain there was a temple.
In the temple there was a little ghost.
It went into a coffin.
*Creak creak*
Did I mix up the stories?
What did I do to deserve this?
Boss Li.
I advise you to hurry up and sleep.
Sister Cai is telling you such a wonderful story.
Isn't it just
to make you sleep?
As long as you fall asleep,
Sister Cai will stop.
Sister Cai stops,
and Ms. Liu stays with you permanently?
Dream on.
Even if I'm sleepy,
I won't sleep.
You...
No...
Ms. Liu.
Is it that I don't tell stories well?
Just...
Boss Li and Professor Fan,
the way they are now...
it's all because we didn't take good care of them.
And Sister Cai,
is being very enthusiastic helping out here.
But she told a story...
Don't ask.
As for me,
I'm even worse off than her.
It's okay, Auntie Liu.
Regarding this issue,
it should have been our responsibility anyway.
Please rest assured.
I have
already contacted Yongfeng Nursing School.
I asked them to send two
very professional,
professionally trained nurses.
Don't worry.
Boss Li and Professor Fan's illness
is now in professional hands.
That's wonderful.
From a professional nursing school?
Do they have nursing experience?
Yes.
Let me put it this way.
Washing feet,
scratching backs,
telling stories,
singing lullabies...
they're experts at everything.
Trust me.
The condition of the two elders
will improve very soon,
and they'll recover.
These nurses even
tell stories,
sing lullabies.
Tell.
Sing.
The wind is quiet,
the moon is bright,
leaves cover the window lattice.
Little baby, in your dreams,
smiling so sweetly.
The two of them,
hand in hand,
just floating like this...
Floating...
floating right into the white clouds.
Old Fan,
are you sleepy?
I wouldn't dare not be sleepy.
Otherwise I'll...
Don't talk.
The wind is quiet, the moon is bright,
leaves cover the window lattice.
Got a bite.
Here we go.
Back to real life again.
Life is so good.
Health is the capital of the revolution.
I've got a bite too.
I've got...
Up you go!
What are you laughing at?
I think as long as we watch our health,
we can definitely still
live a happy life for another twenty years.
Right.
Money can't buy old-age...
suffering.
Don't go looking for sickness when you're fine.
Like chugging hot water to fake a cold.
Alright.
There you go again.
Always harping on little things.
Nagging on and on.
Just like my late mother-in-law.
Up you go!
Did she always care about your health too?
Care about my health? Yeah right.
She was always exposing my faults.
She...
was resentful that I stole her youngest daughter away.
She couldn't get over it.
Pretty much like your mindset right now.
What mindset do I have?
Aren't you watching me and Ms. Liu...
you know...
Right?
This time let's see where you
run.
Up you go!
What on earth is this?
Professor Fan,
help me out.
What is this?
Is this an antique?
Take a look.
Is it Western Zhou or Eastern Zhou?
It's from last week.
Last week, Gou'er Ye
threw away this chamber pot.
Why throw a chamber pot in here? Honestly.
Old Fan,
Ms. Liu
to me...
confessed her feelings.
She revealed her true emotions.
Said I
am a business titan,
who commanded thousands of troops.
She also said
I contributed to the great rejuvenation
of the Chinese nation.
You know,
she said
she admires people like me the most.
Here we go.
How did you catch another one?
Are you using base bait or texture bait?
I'm afraid telling you would provoke you.
This is my own special mix.
Ms. Liu helped me mix it.
What?
No way.
Absolutely impossible.
I don't believe it.
If you don't believe it, why are you nervous?
Who's nervous?
What is there to be nervous about? Honestly.
I've got another one.
Up you go!
Gou'er Ye
You are the one I admire the most
With no children
An old welfare recipient
What's there to admire?
There is! So much!
Look at your life
Face to the earth, back to the sky
Sowing and tilling
Without the hard work of you farmers
Where would our food come from?
It's you who fed our generation
So
You are the one I admire most
The most lovable person
The most lovable
Lovable
My girl
I love hearing that
This medicine
I'll take it
Alright
Open wide
Ah
Grandpa Li, Professor Fan, hello
What are you two doing here?
Eavesdropping at your age?
Naughty
Don't talk nonsense, we weren't eavesdropping
Gou'er Ye wouldn't take his medicine
Right
What are you doing here?
Ms. Liu
Can I ask you a question?
Why do you admire everyone you meet?
It's human nature
It's psychological counseling
With patients
You have to sweet-talk them
Where are you guys going?
My old chronic headache and insomnia
Still haven't gone away
I'm having chills
This tendency to get fevers
Has really set in
See you later
See you
What's wrong?
Why are they...
Sick again?